mama can we get popcorn pretty please no
way [__] you know popcorn at the
movies costs like 200 bucks
but mama you know I have to have my
popcorn when I watch my movies
don't make me piss on the carpet you
ungrateful [__] we're getting a small
yay thank you Mommy
one small popcorn and don't you dare
skimp out on the butter [__] if I'm
paying this much I want that [__]
filled to the brim and overflowing with
popcorny goodness
that's quite a big family you got there
you sure you just want a small don't
even try it you may have got my brother
by the smelly balls with those limited
edition popcorn buckets but it won't
work on me I stopped by the gas station
on the way here to get one dollar
takitos
wait did you just admit to sneaking and
food
I don't remember admitting [__] I just
said I stopped by the gas station so
mind your own business before I talk to
your manager and get you fired
foreign
go on babe excuse me
I have a dollar can I get five tickets
to Megan the spooky doll please
starts damn bro is it just me or does
Uncle Chuck look kind of cute when he
gets excited yahiri does like a wee
little baby haha
even more than that robot baby hip
Hedgehog
that's hot it's about it B is here and
he's wearing his making cosplayer
costume Bartleby please [__] me that's a
crazy dude
wow look at that he looks just like
Megan from the movie it's so much better
than Uncle Chuck's costume and it
doesn't even smell like Bud Light quick
get out your Android phones let's go
take pictures of him instead
and maybe after the movie is over Sonic
can have some alone time with those pics
in the bathroom
yeah he might need to go crap that's
right what you're seeing is the very
same costume that will be worn in the
movie we will all be watching here today
I went to the actual movie set and
bought it with a lot of money
uh-huh where did you get your costume
old man the flea market or did you pull
it out of a dumpster
what is that I smell is that a little
bit of stinky poo poo perhaps a hint of
pea stains maybe uh-huh embarrassing one
ticket to Megan please the IMAX version
of course so I don't have to sit next to
him oh my gosh that stinks
stop walking New Road under [__]
and aren't you coming to see me again
the brand new hit horror comedy of 2023
with me
yeah of course I thought that's where we
were going
oh I see you bought the poor person
tickets didn't you that's so stupid
I bought the IMAX version because I have
more money than your ass
I'm sorry to hear that well if you want
me to go in with you if I ask my mom no
love you want to spend time with your
mother and dirty Uncle we can spend time
together another time
you know you could always come in with
us anyway the employees don't even check
the tickets I bet you can walk Ryden
cool you sneaky little snake you very
well I'll try to away for once
Devin we've talked about this I am not
going to let you go about dating that
man you only just turned 18. but Dad
it's legal and it's not even that big of
an age Gap anyway
Devin he is a 49 year old man also he's
my boss at JC Penney's
look Phil I get your concern but your
son is now my [__] like Sonic the
Hedgehog used to Bartleby that's all
there is to it Haters Gonna Hate
I think it's wonderful that you'll draw
whatever
no one asked for your input [__]
you understand what you're going through
history
but he works at JC Penney's he thinks
that is wonderfully called
you know what maybe I had the wrong
impression of you tell you what after
the movie is over let's head back to my
place and we can crack open a cold beer
together
I'd like that fail
come on given let's continue our 10th
anniversary see you at work tomorrow
well this place is packed like a can of
sardines come on [__] let's go sit down
at the best seats in the House
oh and where is that
what do you think my little Turkish
delight the middle of course you mean
we'll be in front of everyone
we should be fine if anyone smells your
stinky crack we will just move
of course the biggest most muscular guy
in the room has to sit right in front of
me
just my [__] luck
do you want to switch
shut up Jill I'm going to sit here and
stare at the back of his head so he can
feel my glares of the stain all
throughout the movie
that will teach him a lesson for sitting
in front of me the one and only by
Wilson
why do you always say your name like
that nobody knows who you are Brian
baby where are you going the movie is
going to start any second now
it was wrong of me to come here the IMAX
is the only place for someone with money
like me
[Music]
but at air I don't want to see Avatar 2
The Way of the water
I want to see Megan kill some [__]
with my friends don't be like that
Avatar 2 is a great flick one that
speaks to the soul
doesn't the story about indigenous blue
alien people and their white saviors
sound appealing to you
we aren't even indigenous people anymore
Granddad we live in a white superb
neighborhood in the United States of
America
also you just bought a massage chair on
Craigslist
Now cover up your extra pronounced
wrinkly nipples you freak you better
watch your mouth back when I was a kid
we would kill and it you for saying such
things
for telling the truth
yes
everyone make way this
multi-trillionaire has to pee out of his
balls
thank my guy is that your boyfriend he's
pretty freaking cute
I wonder why his butt is so big I wonder
if it's because there's so much poop
stuffed in there
hey Mindy want some McNuggets from my 20
piece spicy chicken McNuggets box I'm
only going to pleasure myself with about
17 of them
thanks Mandy but I'm on a diet right now
manic bought me a new bikini made for
four year olds so I need to fit into it
by swimsuit season
in that case have some of my Sprite it's
clear like water that's how you know it
doesn't have any calories
oh I'm so nervous hopefully Megan isn't
too scary I would hate to put my leaf I
heard it's not even that scary
apparently they cut it down to be PG-13
oh really that's nice
you know what's funny we've been
standing here for two and a half minutes
and you still didn't buy me nachos like
I told you to [__] but Mandy you never
said that I know because you refuse to
acknowledge my existence
[__] go buy me some nachos
hmm
hey Mindy how much of that nacho cheese
do you think I can put in my monster
truck sized ass before I'm forced to
[__] it out my butthole
you know Mandy sometimes you can be a
real [__] you know that like in a
sexy kind of way though
no like a [__]
what who are you calling [__] for God's
sake Mindy when did you get so soft
isn't it bad enough that you're wearing
a shirt in public why don't you have you
tits out how will you be able to bounce
them when people ask you to when was the
last time a guy had used out his balls
mine was over there behind that hot dog
stand
[Music]
thank you
s for your own health take as long as
you need I don't mind waiting others
might get a bit anxious though if you
don't pick up the pace soon some people
even others who are autistic as is the
case here they're sometimes incapable
what does this [__] saying is she
[__]
I'm also autistic
maybe I should walk away no [__]
because don't show weaknesses itself the
way people would expect it to for
example I'm afraid of commitment because
relationships are scary and a lot of
people God I really need to poop I
wonder if I can use this bucket and
blame it on manic
it wouldn't be the first time Spotlight
to speak we would all become more
inclusive and supportive overall
by the way I see you have an avatar
ticket oh my God
[Music]
mom can I have some money to go buy some
Skittles before Megan starts no eat your
turkey toes
oh okay fine but just one box no I want
to
okay too just don't hurt me
you don't say [__] about this you got
that it would be a shame if you
disappeared
what the hell is that Knuckles over
there and next to him is no way are they
hanging out together weird I've never
seen Knuckles talking to other girls
before is he that popular
no he can't be he's a shorty has weird
hair he's kinda mean too and noisy
then again he's also pretty cute
oh Christ he's got one good point about
him that's way too many points for one
person to have at any given time
I should do something
well it was fun talking with you and by
talking I mean you ignoring me for three
straight minutes while I blabber away ha
ha sorry to be a bother
up high nox funny seeing you here I
wasn't about to do anything [__] up or
anything
why the hell do you have a gun
oh this it's only a water gun nothing to
worry about
now this this is where daddy belongs yes
the premium IMAX theater
all by my lonesome on the throne of
loneliness
with only one other guy here besides me
this movie sucks when are the two little
girls going to kiss on the upside I can
Putt and there's no one around to smell
it
foreign
let alone my own blood
that evil doll goes against everything
our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ died
for she is a demon
she's a robot you [__]
you can't make me watch Avatar too and
you can't order me around you just pay
the rent in the house that I live and
you're the one who is my [__]
foreign
you're not supposed to be in here this
is an employee's only Lounge
and why are you naked
close that hole under your nose before I
tear out your Beating Heart and feast
upon it like a meatball
oh my God man you need to take a chill
pill are you off your Maids or some [__]
how dare you use the lord's name in vain
I will ignore the laws of this land and
kill you for that
[__] this I'm calling the cops Ronald go
get me my Android phone
not if anything to say about it I have
[Music]
[Applause]
the previous
[Music]
foreign
something happened to the movie I think
it's broken
that's it
you will not stand for this
then why are you standing up
this
is
knowledge
inside
the demon crawls up from hell at last
the way of the water fans the time to
attack is now
don't let her poison your minds with her
terrible rated Blockbuster film
ah
everyone look the two main characters of
Avatar 2 and Meghan are fighting each
other
wait a second that's not a Pandora from
Avatar that's just a naked old man
[Laughter]
that is enough all of you well your
excitement you filthy animals
foreign
I don't believe what I'm seeing I am
appalled look at you all acting like
children who don't get spanked by their
mama
are we not all moviegoers that share a
hobby why must we fight and pick side up
in this [__]
both ever to The Last Airbender and
Megan deserve to be watched and enjoyed
by many
who are we to put down what each other
love I say we rise up together and prove
once and for all that we are all one and
the same
unless you hate Sonic Underground in
that case I can personally show you the
door but hers for the rest of you follow
me
[Music]
you know what he's right I'm sorry for
calling Avatar [__]
yeah and I apologize for taking a rag
dump in your mouth
[Music]
with the pro the day is saved it's a
damn shame we didn't get to see Megan
today
although if you ask me I think we got to
see something even better
yet and Uncle Chuck looks happy too
together
[Music]
together together
brothers and sisters together
[Music]